it's time to play Etsy
[Music]
pitchmen and well there's no Vanna to be
like here's this thing uh in the real
world retail stores go out of business
when they can't pay rent but on Etsy you
can sell any kind of weird crap make no
money to keep your doors open as long as
they don't take your computer so I'm
going to show you some strange Etsy
items uh and for 250 points you have to
give me a killer tagline to help sell it
all right so here we go the first one
furry panties furry
jeez those are nice I got
one all right ready yes furry panties
everybody's murking for the weekend hey
nice nice good Lover Boy Yes points yes
please I've got one sure no seriously
I've got done no that's not it wait wait
there's more you've heard of Sasquatch
try a new
Sasquatch try new hey I bet you can't
wait to get your big foot in there
yeah all right the tagline sells it
here's this next one kit puppet kind of
sad kind of if you have $45 you don't
like anymore that's what you can do with
that yes Reese now this looks like the
perfect thing to leave behind in the bed
after you've had a one night stand
[Laughter]
and
just as you're hting off a little trait
for the uh you know yes because that
could never be worse than what they
would see when they wake up with you the
next morning like see how much worse it
could have
been all right okay next one Lady Gaga
meat shoes size
seven size seven yes Eliza these shoes
available at lady Meat Locker nice well
played genius a good one points points
all right next one crochet poop crochet
poop
it's really just a pile of yarn yeah
Michael Chay I think it's time to change
grandma that's how she's letting
everyone know that's how she's letting
everyone know points
[Applause]
points